[
	{
		"question": "Что ты хочешь сказать?",
		"answer": "What do you want to say?",
    },
	{
		"question": "Что выглядит странным?",
		"answer": "Whats look strange?",
    },
	{
		"question": "Кого ты знаешь?",
		"answer": "Who do you know?",
	},
	{
		"question": "Кто знает это?",
		"answer": "Who know it?",
	},
	{
		"question": "Кого ты знаешь?",
		"answer": "Who do you know?",
	},
	{
		"question": "Какого рода книги ты читаешь?",
		"answer": "What kind of books do you read?",
	},
	{
		"question": "В какое время ты встаешь?",
		"answer": "What time do you got up?",
	},
	{
		"question": "Сколько денег у тебя с собой?",
		"answer": "How much money do you have with you?",
	},
	{
		"question": "Мне нравится это",
		"answer": "I like it",
	},
	{
		"question": "Кого ты знаешь?",
		"answer": "Who do you know?",
	},
	{
		"question": "Изучать Английский язык быстро",
		"answer": "Learn English fast",
	},
	{
		"question": "Говорить на Английском языке правильно",
		"answer": "Speak English correctly",
	},
	{
		"question": "Хорошая работа",
		"answer": "Good job",
	},
	{
		"question": "Прямо сейчас",
		"answer": "Right now",
	},
	{
		"question": "Еще один раз",
		"answer": "One more time",
	},
	{
		"question": "Я хочу жить за границей",
		"answer": "I want to live abroad",
	},
	{
		"question": "Спасибо большое",
		"answer": "Thanks a lot",
	},
	{
		"question": "Миллион раз спасибо",
		"answer": "Thanks a million",
	},
	{
		"question": "Упасть",
		"answer": "Fell down",
	},
	{
		"question": "Перерыв",
		"answer": "Break time",
	},
	{
		"question": "Поддерживать",
		"answer": "Keep up",
	},
	{
		"question": "Решать эту проблему",
		"answer": "Solve this problem",
	},
	{
		"question": "Они дома",
		"answer": "They are at home",
	},
	{
		"question": "Теряться",
		"answer": "Get lost",
	},
	{
		"question": "Время от времени",
		"answer": "From time to time",
	},
	{
		"question": "Поднять голову",
		"answer": "Head up",
	},
	{
		"question": "Платить за нее",
		"answer": "Pay for her",
	},
	{
		"question": "Как можно быстрее",
		"answer": "As soon as possible",
	},
	{
		"question": "Упасть",
		"answer": "Fell over",
	},
	{
		"question": "Садиться",
		"answer": "Sit down",
	},
	{
		"question": "Отдыхать на выходных",
		"answer": "Have on weekends",
	},
	{
		"question": "Работать над чем-то",
		"answer": "Work on",
	},
	{
		"question": "Свободное время",
		"answer": "Free time",
	},
	{
		"question": "Слушать музыку",
		"answer": "Listen to music",
	},
	{
		"question": "Искать работу",
		"answer": "Look for a job",
	},
	{
		"question": "Собираться ложиться спать",
		"answer": "Going to bed",
	},
	{
		"question": "Выйти",
		"answer": "Went out",
	},
	{
		"question": "От них всех",
		"answer": "From them all",
	},
	{
		"question": "Идти назад",
		"answer": "Walk back",
	},
	{
		"question": "Вся правда",
		"answer": "All the trust",
	},
	{
		"question": "Зависеть от тебя",
		"answer": "Depend on you",
	},
	{
		"question": "Произвести впечатление",
		"answer": "Make an impression",
	},
	{
		"question": "Проводить время",
		"answer": "Spend time",
	},
	{
		"question": "Добираться до работы",
		"answer": "Get to work",
	},
	{
		"question": "Какого рода?",
		"answer": "What kind of?",
	},
	{
		"question": "В какое время?",
		"answer": "What time?",
	},
	{
		"question": "Им",
		"answer": "Them",
	},
	{
		"question": "Сколько времени у тебя занимает добраться до работы?",
		"answer": "How long time does it take you to get to work?",
	},
	{
		"question": "Уходить из дома",
		"answer": "Leave home",
	},
	{
		"question": "Высокий",
		"answer": "Tall",
	},
	{
		"question": "Оставаться",
		"answer": "Stay",
	},
	{
		"question": "Скоро",
		"answer": "Soon",
	},
	{
		"question": "Родиться",
		"answer": "Born",
	},
	{
		"question": "В браке",
		"answer": "Married",
	},
	{
		"question": "Деревня",
		"answer": "Village",
	},
	{
		"question": "Доказывать",
		"answer": "Prove",
	},
	{
		"question": "Ожидать",
		"answer": "Expect",
	},
	{
		"question": "Еще",
		"answer": "Yet",
	},
	{
		"question": "Предпочитать",
		"answer": "Prefer",
	},
	{
		"question": "Наличные",
		"answer": "Cash",
	},
	{
		"question": "Вдохновение писать код",
		"answer": "Inspiration to write code",
	},
	{
		"question": "Тревога",
		"answer": "Alarm",
	},
	{
		"question": "Крыша",
		"answer": "Roof",
	},
	{
		"question": "Сомнительно",
		"answer": "Doubtfully",
	},
	{
		"question": "Встречаться",
		"answer": "Meet",
	},
	{
		"question": "Грязь",
		"answer": "Dirt",
	},
	{
		"question": "Сидеть",
		"answer": "Sit",
	},
	{
		"question": "Привычный",
		"answer": "Habitual",
	},
	{
		"question": "Платье",
		"answer": "Dress",
	},
	{
		"question": "Квартира",
		"answer": "Flat",
	},
	{
		"question": "Улучшать",
		"answer": "Improve",
	},
	{
		"question": "Лучше",
		"answer": "Better",
	},
	{
		"question": "Грамматика",
		"answer": "Grammar",
	},
	{
		"question": "Правильный",
		"answer": "Correct",
	},
	{
		"question": "Использовать (не use)",
		"answer": "Employ",
	},
	{
		"question": "Пачкать",
		"answer": "Sully",
	},
	{
		"question": "Мудрый",
		"answer": "Sage",
	},
	{
		"question": "Состоять",
		"answer": "Consist",
	},
	{
		"question": "Недоумение",
		"answer": "Perplexity",
	},
	{
		"question": "Приносить",
		"answer": "Bring",
	},
	{
		"question": "Тугой",
		"answer": "Tight",
	},
	{
		"question": "Соотношение",
		"answer": "Ratio",
	},
	{
		"question": "Купить",
		"answer": "Buy",
	},
	{
		"question": "Платить",
		"answer": "Pay",
	},
	{
		"question": "Снова",
		"answer": "Again",
	},
	{
		"question": "За границу",
		"answer": "Abroad",
	},
	{
		"question": "Другой",
		"answer": "Another",
	},
	{
		"question": "Обед",
		"answer": "Lunch",
	},
	{
		"question": "Стать",
		"answer": "Become",
	},
	{
		"question": "Обсуждать",
		"answer": "Discuss",
	},
	{
		"question": "Привлекать",
		"answer": "Attract",
	},
	{
		"question": "Рекомендовать",
		"answer": "Recommend",
	},
	{
		"question": "Партнер",
		"answer": "Partner",
	},
	{
		"question": "Счастье",
		"answer": "Happiness",
	},
	{
		"question": "Какие-либо (любые)",
		"answer": "Any",
	},
	{
		"question": "Вообще (совсем)",
		"answer": "At all",
	},
	{
		"question": "Совет",
		"answer": "Advice",
	},
	{
		"question": "Меньше",
		"answer": "Less",
	},
	{
		"question": "Единственное число",
		"answer": "Singular",
	},
	{
		"question": "Множественное число",
		"answer": "Plural",
	},
	{
		"question": "Заказывать",
		"answer": "Order",
	},
	{
		"question": "Мотивировать",
		"answer": "Motivate",
	},
	{
		"question": "Объяснять",
		"answer": "Explain",
	},
	{
		"question": "Тренировать",
		"answer": "Train",
	},
	{
		"question": "Память",
		"answer": "Memory",
	},
	{
		"question": "Регулярно",
		"answer": "Regularly",
	},
	{
		"question": "Самообразование",
		"answer": "Self-education",
	},
	{
		"question": "Решение",
		"answer": "Decision",
	},
	{
		"question": "Зал",
		"answer": "Gym",
	},
	{
		"question": "Достаточно",
		"answer": "Enaugh",
	},
	{
		"question": "Знания",
		"answer": "Knowledge",
	},
	{
		"question": "Услышать (слушать)",
		"answer": "Hear",
	},
	{
		"question": "Покой",
		"answer": "Peace",
	},
	{
		"question": "Пугать маленьких детей",
		"answer": "Frighten little children",
	},
	{
		"question": "Ужасный",
		"answer": "Terrible",
	},
	{
		"question": "Биение",
		"answer": "Beating",
	},
	{
		"question": "Стоять",
		"answer": "Stand",
	},
	{
		"question": "Муж",
		"answer": "Husbend",
	},
	{
		"question": "Кричать",
		"answer": "Cry",
	},
	{
		"question": "Похороны",
		"answer": "Feneral",
	},
	{
		"question": "Пугать",
		"answer": "Frighten",
	},
	{
		"question": "Завещание",
		"answer": "Will",
	},
	{
		"question": "Трясет",
		"answer": "Shaking",
	},
	{
		"question": "Подготовить",
		"answer": "Prepare",
	},
	{
		"question": "Туман",
		"answer": "Fog",
	},
	{
		"question": "Дышать вместе с тобой",
		"answer": "Breathe with you",
	},
	{
		"question": "Накануне",
		"answer": "Eve",
	},
	{
		"question": "Страх",
		"answer": "Fear",
	},
	{
		"question": "Вместе",
		"answer": "Together",
	},
	{
		"question": "Важный",
		"answer": "Important",
	},
	{
		"question": "Отличный",
		"answer": "Excellent",
	},
	{
		"question": "Экзамен",
		"answer": "Exam",
	},
	{
		"question": "Блестяще",
		"answer": "Brilliant",
	},
	{
		"question": "Жаловаться на плохую жизнь",
		"answer": "Complain about a bad life",
	},
	{
		"question": "Отказываться от лишних денег",
		"answer": "Refuse extra money",
	},
	{
		"question": "Добавить",
		"answer": "Add",
	},
	{
		"question": "Беспокоить",
		"answer": "Worry",
	},
	{
		"question": "Фильм",
		"answer": "Movie",
	},
	{
		"question": "Разные",
		"answer": "Different",
	},
	{
		"question": "Напиток",
		"answer": "Drink",
	},
	{
		"question": "Уходить",
		"answer": "Leave",
	},
	{
		"question": "Упражнение",
		"answer": "Exercise",
	},
	{
		"question": "Трудно",
		"answer": "Difficult",
	},
	{
		"question": "Что твой босс обычно обещает?",
		"answer": "What does your boss usually promise?",
	},
	{
		"question": "Я наслаждаюсь изучением Английского языка",
		"answer": "I enjoy learn English",
	},
	{
		"question": "Сколько по времени занимает у его дочери добраться в школу?",
		"answer": "How long does it take his daughter to get to school?",
	},
	{
		"question": "Почему твоя мама думает так?",
		"answer": "Why does your mother think so?"
	}
]
